So if a photon is directed
through a plane with two slits in it
and either slit is observed,
it will not go through both slits.
If it's unobserved, it will.
However, if it's observed
after it's left the plane
but before it hits its target,
it won't have gone through both slits.
Agreed.
What's your point?
There's no point, I just think
it's a good idea for a T-shirt.
- Excuse me.
- Hang on.
One across is "Aegean."
Eight down is "Nabokov."
26 across is "MCM."
14 down is...
Move your finger...
"Phylum" which makes 14 across
"Port-au-Prince"
See, "Papa Doc's capitol idea,"
that's "Port-au-Prince."
Haiti.
- Can I help you?
- Yes.
Is this the high-IQ sperm bank?
If you have to ask,
maybe you shouldn't be here.
I think this is the place.
- Fill these out.
- Thank you.
- We'll be right back.
- Take your time.
I'll just finish my crossword puzzle.
Oh, wait.
Leonard, I don't think I can do this.
What, are you kidding?
You're a semi-pro.
No. We are committing genetic fraud.
There's no guarantee that our sperm
is going to generate high-IQ offspring.
Think about that. I have a sister with
the same basic DNA mix
who hostesses at Fuddruckers.
Sheldon, this was your idea.
A little extra money to get fractional
T-1 bandwidth in the apartment.
I know, and I do yearn
for faster downloads.
But there's some poor woman
who's gonna pin her hopes on my sperm.
What if she winds up with a toddler
who doesn't know if he should use
an integral or a differential
to solve the area under a curve?
- I'm sure she'll still love him.
- I wouldn't.
Well, what do you want to do?
I want to leave.
What's the protocol for leaving?
I don't know... I've never reneged
on a proffer of sperm before.
Let's try just walking out.
- Bye.
- Bye. Nice meeting you.